Advanced features of this website require that you enable JavaScript in your browser. Thank you!

[

](https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/)

Clear History and Accounts

Primary Menu
------------

Menu

Search for:   

Privacy Policy
==============

By using this website, you accept all the terms and conditions of the [deletehistoryfree.com](https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/) Privacy Policy. The purpose of the deletehistoryfree.com Privacy Policy is to inform you what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit deletehistoryfree.com and how we may use it. This privacy practice applies only to deletehistoryfree.com, and not to other websites to which we may link. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the website.

_Information Collection and Use_  
deletehistoryfree.com does not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically provide it to us.  
deletehistoryfree.com automatically gathers and records usage information such as your browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query; numbers and frequency of visits to different areas. This data is used to help us determine how much our visitors use specific parts of our website and to estimate the total number of users visiting deletehistoryfree.com from specific countries or regions of the world, so we can improve our website. We may use the information we gather to understand our users base, improve the quality of our services.  
deletehistoryfree.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

_Cookies_  
deletehistoryfree.com uses cookies to give you a more personalised web experience, make the website more user-friendly and efficient. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or device and saved by your browser. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to reject all cookies, accept cookies from certain websites only or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of our website may not function properly if you reject cookies. We use session cookies that are automatically deleted after you close your browser. (See [how to clear cookies](https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/how-to-delete-cookies/)).  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on deletehistoryfree.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  

_Information Sharing and Disclosure_  
deletehistoryfree.com may share aggregated statistical information about users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. We do not share personal information that you may give us to any third-parties.

_Links to other sites_  
deletehistoryfree.com provides links to third-party sites, which are not under the control of deletehistoryfree.com. deletehistoryfree.com is not responsible for the content and privacy policy on third-party sites.

_Changes to the Privacy Policy_  
The deletehistoryfree.com Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy page periodically for any changes at: https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/privacy-policy

Click to rate this post!

\[Total: 1 Average: 3\]

Footer Content
--------------

Using [Tiny Framework](http://mtomas.com/1/tiny-forge-free-mobile-first-wordpress-theme) • [Log in](https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/wp-login.php)

This website uses cookies and ads to improve the user experience. We asume you accept this. If not you may leave.Accept [Read More](https://www.deletehistoryfree.com/privacy-policy/)

Privacy & Cookies Policy

Close

Necessary Always Enabled
